DEVLIN BOOTH

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full stack software developer with experience developing with multiple different technologies. Detail-oriented, organized and meticulous employee. Works at fast pace to meet tight deadlines. Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company success. Complex problem-solver with analytical and driven mindset. Dedicated to achieving demanding development objectives while producing impeccable code. Smart professional with proven troubleshooting and debugging capabilities for resolving complex technical issues.

WORK HISTORY

Software Engineer, 03/2023 - Current HackForLA, Remote, Los Angeles, CA

- Website Team hackforla.org
- Full Stack Developer, working remotely across teams to complete design issues using Kanban and continuous integration/continuous delivery (CI/CD) methodology
- Contribute to open-source Hack for LA website repository through issue completion, code review

Software Engineering Associate, 06/2022 - Current General Assembly, Remote

- Guided over 90 students through the rigorous transformational journey of becoming a full stack software developer.
- Facilitate understanding of key full stack concepts including: data structures, languages, front-end libraries, database design (sql/nosql), web frameworks, and much more!
- Provide hands-on instruction in a safe, supportive, and energetic environment; welcoming students with diverse needs and learning styles.
- Selected to pilot new blended learning program.
- Leverage strong communication skills while educating students in developing Full Stack applications

Software Engineering Apprentice, 11/2022 - 02/2023 App Academy, Remote

- 450 hour apprenticeship building upon existing knowledge as well as learning new tech!
- Completed over 1000 code challenges, projects, and course materials to strengthen core software engineering concepts.
- Utilized Mocha/Chai testing frameworks and assertion libraries to implement test driven development at unit, integration and End-2-End test levels.
- Added plethora of tech to my already diverse arsenal of software tech tools.



Los Angeles, CA 90046



5044306996



adevlin.booth@gmail.com

LINKS:

- linkedin.com/in/devlin-booth/
- github.com/adevlinb
- devlin-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- Python Django
- PostgreSQL
- Sequelize
- Docker
- Mocha / Chai testing
- API Design

EDUCATION

Certificate, Software Engineering **General Assembly** - Remote, Los Angeles, CA

Bachelor of Science, Urban Planning University of New Orleans - New Orleans, LA

Master of Arts, Landscape Architecture Louisiana State University - Baton Rouge